here at the NFL combine with general
manager George Payeyton. George, on the
heels of an AFC Championship game
appearance. What are the keys over the
next few months to continue to build
this roster and put yourself in position
for the 2026 season?
>> You know, we had [music] few weeks of
meetings after the season and it just
kind of determine where our needs are,
you know, where our musts are and then
you kind of weigh the draft compared to
free agency and then you kind of fill
them through there. And so it's it's uh
[music] man, the next three weeks, the
next four weeks, we're just grinding,
you know, free agency and then the
draft. And you try to film through
those.
>> I know it comes quickly when you when
you make it that far. The draft is part
of that. Obviously, when you're picking
30th later in the first round, [music]
does the process change at all? Are
there any more difficulties? And and how
does this combine help you prepare for
that pick?
>> I mean, it helps us prepare just to get
to know the players. You know, the more
we get to know these players, the better
decisions we'll make. [music] I mean,
picking 30 is kind of cool. I mean, just
you like to pick 30, 31, 32. Um, you can
just kind of wait. Maybe you don't have
the the pressure of of up top. You kind
of wait and see what the best players
fall and and if someone's falling, maybe
you can go up and get them. Um, maybe
you can move back, but you know, kind of
like picking 30.
>> And then George, obviously free agency
is coming up, but we can't forget about
all the extensions you've done over the
last 18 months. [music] 10 10 in last 18
months, I believe. How much flexibility
has it given you to get those deals done
before free agency? And uh how does it
set you up for this free agency period?
>> Well, I just think you look at the
players we extended. I mean, all the pro
bowlers, the all pros, defensive player
of the year, so we got 10 out of the
way. [music] Um we've done six since
August, you know, 400 million. And just
think if we didn't get those guys done,
what their market would be. And so we
got ahead of it. They're all really good
players, even [music] better um
teammates, better people. And so we're
really fortunate to get ahead of it.
Perfect. George, thanks for your time.
Thank you. Appreciate it.